What're you doing?
I'm making leaf-fish.
I see...
Looks pretty good.
This one's a fish and this one's an octopus!
It's not a starfish?
Huh?
Uh... S-Sorry...
The Starfish Shrine of Books
Rin... Want this?
Ah! A fish book!
A Picture
Encyclopedia
of Fish
A Picture
Encyclopedia
of Fish
A Picture
Encyclopedia
of Fish
A Picture
Encyclopedia
of Fish
A Picture
Encyclopedia
of Fish
A Picture
Encyclopedia
of Fish
That's a salmon! It has a lightly salted flavour!
You think of them as food?
Look, it's a righteye flounder!
Righteye flounder?
That fish with both its eyes on the same side.
Looks like it, right?
Ah! You're right!
Look at this one, then!
It's like a blowfish, huh?
Yeah, I see it too.
Daikichi, look!
Hmm?
No cheating!
What do you mean, cheating?
Cutting them is cheating.
This isn't cheating... It's called grown-up ingenuity.
Ah! What should I do?!
They're all eaten!
Ah! And there are holes in that acorn!
Holes?
Must have been a bug...
Huh?
Huh?!
Ah, we've had that happen too!
I made Reina cry when I told her she
couldn't open them inside the house!
Well, what should I do?
I've got bugs coming out of these acorns...
...and the leaves have been eaten away at.
Leaves?
We like to press them.
Pressed leaves, huh?
I'm home!
Hey, make sure you wash your hands first!
Wait a sec!
Daikichi, I'm leaving!
Leaf Aquarium
「Leaf Aquarium」